{"Imraan": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Al Imran", "wiki_summary": "Imran in Islam is regarded as the father of Mary (mother of Jesus)", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Hud": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Hud (prophet)", "wiki_summary": "Hud was a prophet of ancient Arabia mentioned in the Qur’an", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Aal-Imraan": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Al Imran", "wiki_summary": "Imran in Islam is regarded as the father of Mary (mother of Jesus)", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Qana": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Qana", "wiki_summary": "Qana, also spelled Cana or Kana, (Arabic: قانا‎) is a village in southern Lebanon located 10 kilometres (6.2 mi) southeast of the city of Tyre and 12 kilometres (7.5 mi) north of the border with Israel.", "correction": "GPE"}, "Assam": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Assam", "wiki_summary": "Assam (, Assamese: [ɔxɔm] (listen)) is a state in northeastern India, situated south of the eastern Himalayas along the Brahmaputra and Barak River valleys.", "correction": "GPE"}, "Fatani": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Erithria": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Eritrea", "wiki_summary": "officially the State of Eritrea, is a sovereign state in the Horn of Africa, with its capital at Asmara", "correction": "GPE"}, "Chechnia": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Chechnya", "wiki_summary": "Chechnya, officially the Chechen Republic is a federal subject (a republic) of Russia.", "correction": "GPE"}, "Crusaders": {"original ent_type_": "PRODUCT", "wiki_title": "Crusades", "wiki_summary": "The crusades were a series of religious wars in western Asia and Europe initiated, supported and sometimes directed by the Roman Catholic Church between the 11th and the 17th century.", "correction": "ORG"}, "Mujahid": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Mujahideen", "wiki_summary": "Mujahideen (Arabic: مجاهدين‎ mujāhidīn) is the plural form of mujahid (Arabic: مجاهد‎), the term for one engaged in Jihad (literally, “struggle”).", "correction": "ORG"}, "Mujahideen": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Mujahideen", "wiki_summary": "Mujahideen (Arabic: مجاهدين‎ mujāhidīn) is the plural form of mujahid (Arabic: مجاهد‎), the term for one engaged in Jihad (literally, “struggle”).", "correction": "ORG"}, "Allahu Akbar": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Takbir", "wiki_summary": "The Takbīr (تَكْبِير, Arabic pronunciation: [tækˈbiːr]) is the Arabic phrase Allāhu akbar (الله أكبر), usually translated as \"God is [the] greatest\".", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Patron": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Patronage", "wiki_summary": "The word \"patron\" derives from the Latin: patronus (\"patron\"), one who gives benefits to his clients (see Patronage in ancient Rome)", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Riyal": {"original ent_type_": "LOC", "wiki_title": "Rial", "wiki_summary": "The Saudi riyal is the currency of Saudi Arabia", "correction": "MONEY"}, "Shawwaal": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Shawwal", "wiki_summary": "Shawwāl is the tenth month of the lunar based Islamic calendar", "correction": "DATE"}, "Muharram": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Muharram", "wiki_summary": "Muḥarram (Arabic: المحرّم) is the first month of the Islamic calendar.", "correction": "DATE"}, "Halal": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Halal", "wiki_summary": "Halal (; Arabic: حلال‎ ḥalāl), also spelled hallal or halaal, is an Arabic word that translates to \"permissible\" into English.", "correction": "LAW"}, "Haram": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Haram", "wiki_summary": "Haram (; Arabic: حَرَام‎ ḥarām [ħaˈraːm]) is an Arabic term meaning forbidden.", "correction": "LAW"}, "Exalted": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Exalted", "wiki_summary": "Exalted is a role-playing game published by White Wolf Publishing.", "correction": "nil"}, "Shari'a": {"original ent_type_": "GPE", "wiki_title": "Sharia", "wiki_summary": "Sharia (, Arabic: شريعة‎ [ʃaˈriːʕa]), Islamic law or sharia law is a religious law forming part of the Islamic tradition", "correction": "LAW"}, "infidels": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Infidel", "wiki_summary": "Infidel (literally \"unfaithful\") is a term used in certain religions for those accused of unbelief in the central tenets of their own religion, for members of another religion, or for the irreligious.", "correction": "ORG"}, "Mushrik": {"original ent_type_": "GPE", "wiki_title": "Shirk (Islam)", "wiki_summary": "In Islam, shirk (Arabic: شرك‎ širk) is the sin of idolatry or polytheism, i.e., the deification or worship of anyone or anything besides God, i.e., Allah.", "correction": "LAW"}, "Al-Ma'ida": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Al-Ma'ida", "wiki_summary": "Al Māʼidah (Arabic: المائدة‎, \"The Table\" or \"The Table Spread with Food\", likely a word of Ethiopic origin) is the fifth chapter (sūrah) of the Quran, with 120 verses (āyāt).", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Fatawa": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Fatwa", "wiki_summary": "A fatwā (, also US: ; Arabic: فتوى‎; plural fatāwā فتاوى) is a nonbinding legal opinion on a point of Islamic law (sharia) given by a qualified jurist in response to a question posed by a private individual, judge or government", "correction": "LAW"}, "Jihad": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Jihad", "wiki_summary": "Jihad (English: ; Arabic: جهاد‎ jihād [dʒɪˈhaːd]) is an Arabic word which literally means striving or struggling, especially with a praiseworthy aim.", "correction": "STRUCTURALVIOLENCE"}, "Sunnah": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Sunnah", "wiki_summary": "Sunnah (Arabic: سُنَّة‎, sunnah, plural Arabic: سُنَن‎ sunan [sunan]), also sunna or sunnat, is the body of literature which discusses and prescribes the traditional customs and practices of the Islamic community, both social and legal,[1] often but not necessarily based on the verbally transmitted record of the teachings, deeds and sayings, silent permissions (or disapprovals) of the Islamic prophet Muhammad, as well as various reports about Muhammad's companions.", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Ahlul-Sunnah": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Ahlul-Sunnah", "wiki_summary": "So Ahlus-Sunnah wa'l-Jama'ah have been described with sticking to the Sunnah and [in all circumstances] avoiding / disregarding the invented matters and innovations in the Din (religion)", "correction": "NORP"}, "Rashidoon": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Rashidun", "wiki_summary": "The Rashidun Caliphs (Rightly Guided Caliphs; Arabic: الخلفاء الراشدون‎ al-Khulafāʾu ar-Rāshidūn), often simply called, collectively, \"the Rashidun\", is a term used in Sunni Islam to refer to the 30-year reign of the first four caliphs (successors) following the death of the Islamic prophet Muhammad, namely: Abu Bakr, Umar, Uthman ibn Affan, and Ali of the Rashidun Caliphate, the first caliphate", "correction": "DATE"}, "Imams": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Imam", "wiki_summary": "Imam (/ɪˈmɑːm/; Arabic: إمام‎ imām; plural: أئمة aʼimmah) is an Islamic leadership position", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Riba": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Riba", "wiki_summary": "Riba (Arabic: ربا ,الربا، الربٰوة‎ ribā or al-ribā, IPA: [ˈrɪbæː]) can be roughly translated as \"usury\", or unjust, exploitative gains made in trade or business under Islamic law.", "correction": "STRUCTURALVIOLENCE"}, "Baqarah": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Al-Baqarah", "wiki_summary": "Al-Baqarah (Arabic: البقرة‎, \"The Heifer\" or \"The Cow\") is the second and longest chapter (sūrah) of the Quran.", "correction": "PERSON"}, "SWT": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "SWT", "wiki_summary": "SWT may refer to: Scottish Wildlife Trust, a charity in Scotland Subhanahu wa ta'ala, Arabic for \"The most glorified, the most high\", Muslim honorific Stationary wavelet transform Standard Widget Toolkit, a graphical widget toolkit for use with the Java platform Slaithwaite railway station, England; National Rail station code South West Trains, a former train operating company in southern England", "correction": "nil"}, "Grace": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Grace", "wiki_summary": "", "correction": "nil"}, "The Nobel": {"original ent_type_": "WORK_OF_ART", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "nil"}, "Holy Places": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Holy place", "wiki_summary": "A holy place is a place that people consider holy and/or a religion considers to be of special religious significance.", "correction": "LOC"}, "Seerah": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Prophetic biography", "wiki_summary": "In Islam, Al-sīra al-Nabawiyya (Prophetic biography), Sīrat Rasūl Allāh (Life of the Messenger of God), or Seerah are the traditional Muslim biographies of Muhammad from which, in addition to the Quran and trustable Hadiths, most historical information about his life and the early period of Islam is derived.", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Makka": {"original ent_type_": "FAC", "wiki_title": "Mecca", "wiki_summary": "Mecca, also spelled Makkah, is a city in the Hejazi region of Saudi Arabia.", "correction": "GPE"}, "Kuffar": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Kafir", "wiki_summary": "Kafir (Arabic: كافر‎ kāfir; plural كَافِرُونَ kāfirūna, كفّار kuffār or كَفَرَة kafarah; feminine كافرة kāfirah; feminine plural كافرات kāfirāt or كوافر kawāfir) is an Arabic term (from the root K-F-R \"to cover\") meaning \"infidel\", \"rejector\", \"disbeliever\", \"unbeliever\", \"nonbeliever\".", "correction": "PERSON"}, "A.H": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "nil"}, "Kaferoon": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Kafir (plural)", "wiki_summary": "Kafir (Arabic: كافر‎ kāfir; plural كَافِرُونَ kāfirūna, كفّار kuffār or كَفَرَة kafarah; feminine كافرة kāfirah; feminine plural كافرات kāfirāt or كوافر kawāfir) is an Arabic term (from the root K-F-R \"to cover\") meaning \"infidel\",[1] \"rejector\",[2] \"disbeliever\", \"unbeliever\", \"nonbeliever\".", "correction": "ORG"}, "Hubal": {"original ent_type_": "LOC", "wiki_title": "Hubal", "wiki_summary": "Hubal (Arabic: هُبَل‎) was a god worshipped in pre-Islamic Arabia, notably by Quraysh at the Kaaba in Mecca.", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Arabian": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Arabian Peninsula", "wiki_summary": "The Arabian Peninsula, or simply Arabia (; Arabic:", "correction": "LOC"}, "Taghut": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Taghut", "wiki_summary": "Taghut (ar. طاغوت,", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Torah": {"original ent_type_": "GPE", "wiki_title": "Torah", "wiki_summary": "It can most specifically mean the first five books (Pentateuch or five books of Moses) of the 24 books of the Tanakh (Hebrew Bible)", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Prophets": {"original ent_type_": "WORK_OF_ART", "wiki_title": "Prophet", "wiki_summary": "In religion, a prophet is an individual who is regarded as being in contact with a divine being and is said to speak on that entity's behalf, serving as an intermediary with humanity by delivering messages or teachings from the supernatural source to other people.", "correction": "PERSON"}, "iii": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "nil", "wiki_summary": "nil", "correction": "nil"}, "Shariah": {"original ent_type_": "NORP", "wiki_title": "Sharia", "wiki_summary": "Sharia (, Arabic: شريعة‎ [ʃaˈriːʕa]), Islamic law or sharia law is a religious law forming part of the Islamic tradition.", "correction": "LAW"}, "subdual": {"original ent_type_": "GPE", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "nil"}, "Quran": {"original ent_type_": "PRODUCT", "wiki_title": "Quran", "wiki_summary": "The Quran ( kor-AHN; Arabic: القرآن‎, romanized: al-Qurʼān Arabic pronunciation: [alqur'ʔaːn], literally meaning \"the recitation\"), also romanized Qur'an or Koran, is the central religious text of Islam, which Muslims believe to be a revelation from God (Allah).", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Divine": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Divinity", "wiki_summary": "In religion, divinity or Godhead is the state of things that are believed to come from a supernatural power or deity, such as God, the supreme being, creator deity, or spirits, and are therefore regarded as sacred and holy.", "correction": "nil"}, "Absolute Authority": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "nil"}, "Usury": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Usury", "wiki_summary": "Usury () is the practice of making unethical or immoral monetary loans that unfairly enrich the lender.", "correction": "STRUCTURALVIOLENCE"}, "xi": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "nil", "wiki_summary": "nil", "correction": "nil"}, "Qunduz": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Kunduz Province", "wiki_summary": "Kunduz or Qunduz (Persian: قندوز‎, Pashto: کندوز‎) is one of the 34 provinces of Afghanistan, located in the northern part of the country next to Tajikistan.", "correction": "GPE"}, "the Islamic Nation": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "the Islamic Nation", "wiki_summary": "nil", "correction": "NORP"}, "The Nation of Martyrdom": {"original ent_type_": "WORK_OF_ART", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "ORG"}, "Quran 3:169-171": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "", "wiki_summary": "WORK_OF_ART", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "Crusades": {"original ent_type_": "PRODUCT", "wiki_title": "Crusades", "wiki_summary": "The crusades were a series of religious wars in western Asia and Europe initiated, supported and sometimes directed by the Roman Catholic Church between the 11th and the 17th century.", "correction": "STRUCTURALVIOLENCE"}, "the American Sixth Fleet": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "PRODUCT"}, "Time": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Time", "wiki_summary": "Time is the indefinite continued progress of existence and events that occur in an apparently irreversible succession from the past, through the present, to the future.", "correction": "WORK_OF_ART"}, "scrutinises": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "no wiki reference", "wiki_summary": "no wiki reference", "correction": "nil"}, "Halliburton": {"original ent_type_": "PERSON", "wiki_title": "Halliburton", "wiki_summary": "Halliburton Company is an American multinational corporation.", "correction": "ORG"}, "Guardian": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Guardian", "wiki_summary": "Guardian may refer to: Legal guardian, a person with the authority and duty to care for the interests of anotherGuardian(s) or The Guardian(s) may also refer to:", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Helper": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Helper", "wiki_summary": "nil", "correction": "PERSON"}, "Guidance": {"original ent_type_": "ORG", "wiki_title": "Guidance", "wiki_summary": "Guidance may refer to: What a guide gives Guidance (album), by American instrumental rock band Russian Circles", "correction": "nil"}}